<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Rishabh Naik</title><link>https://rishabhnaik.netlify.app/</link><description>Recent content on Rishabh Naik</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2008–2019, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 22:34:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rishabhnaik.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Its Hard for you, not for me</title><link>https://rishabhnaik.netlify.app/posts/its-hard-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 22:34:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://rishabhnaik.netlify.app/posts/its-hard-for-you/</guid><description>Coming soon&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://rishabhnaik.netlify.app/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 21:40:31 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://rishabhnaik.netlify.app/about/</guid><description>Hey, My name is Rishabh. I am an Engineering student at Sambhram Institute of Technology, Bangalore. I am also a VKSSF scholar and a mentee at Sushiksha programme. An aspiring Digital artist creating his own dimensions of art.</description></item><item><title>Display Your Progress</title><link>https://rishabhnaik.netlify.app/posts/display-your-progress/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 16:04:55 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://rishabhnaik.netlify.app/posts/display-your-progress/</guid><description>This is my first blog that is highly written on my experiences. The series of upcoming blogs contain all the things that I did on that particular week and the things that I learnt. A focused group of ours from Sushiksha sit for a call every night at 9:30 pm at IST to talk about the day. Every month we had to set five goals as Pentathlon(Ultraworking), which consists of goals like fitness, Wake-up / Sleep cycle, Most important work (MIW), Nutrition and Planning.</description></item><item><title>Next Gen Art</title><link>https://rishabhnaik.netlify.app/posts/next-gen-art/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 13:00:10 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://rishabhnaik.netlify.app/posts/next-gen-art/</guid><description>Digital Art Art is a form to express our feelings and emotions. It can also visualize our thoughts on a canvas. From the beginning of the Stone age till now, we have been using pictures or drawings to tell stories. In the stone age, humans used to draw on the wall with whatever they had in their hand. They would take fruit and draw with their rich colours or sometimes use charcoal as a pencil.</description></item></channel></rss>