<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Rishabh Naik</title><link>/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Rishabh Naik</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 22:34:01 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Its a hardship</title><link>/blog/post/its-hard-for-you/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 22:34:01 +0530</pubDate><guid>/blog/post/its-hard-for-you/</guid><description>The tougher the work the more we will enjoy,I have made digital Art for 2 years still it was hard for me. But after this Art, it was not. As you may all know now, I originally made digital illustrations and posted them on Instagram. In a long time, I hadn&amp;rsquo;t done mechanical illustrations. This time I was thinking of making a Superbike, but I did not know which one to do.</description></item><item><title>Display Your Progress</title><link>/blog/post/display-your-progress/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 16:04:55 +0530</pubDate><guid>/blog/post/display-your-progress/</guid><description>This is my first blog that is highly written on my experiences. The series of upcoming blogs contain all the things that I did on that particular week and the things that I learnt. A focused group of ours from Sushiksha sit for a call every night at 9:30 pm at IST to talk about the day. Every month we had to set five goals as Pentathlon(Ultraworking), which consists of goals like fitness, Wake-up / Sleep cycle, Most important work (MIW), Nutrition and Planning.</description></item><item><title>Next Gen Art</title><link>/blog/post/next-gen-art/</link><pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2021 13:00:10 +0530</pubDate><guid>/blog/post/next-gen-art/</guid><description>Digital Art Art is a form to express our feelings and emotions. It can also visualize our thoughts on a canvas. From the beginning of the Stone age till now, we have been using pictures or drawings to tell stories. In the stone age, humans used to draw on the wall with whatever they had in their hand. They would take fruit and draw with their rich colours or sometimes use charcoal as a pencil.</description></item></channel></rss>